My Fault: London is a drama, romance film directed by Dani Girdwood.
18-year-old Noah moves from America to London, with her mother who's recently
fallen in love with William, a wealthy British businessman.
Noah meets William’s son, bad-boy Nick, and soon discovers there
is an attraction between them neither can avoid.
As Noah spends the summer adjusting to her new life, her devastating past will
catch up with her while falling in love for the first time.
Noah, played by Asha Banks.
Nick, played by Matthew Broome.
Ella, played by Eve Macklin.
William, played by Ray Fearon.
Jenna, played by Enva Lewis.
Travis, played by Jason Flemyng.
My Fault: London is a 2025 British romantic drama film directed by Dani
Girdwood and Charlotte Fassler, and written by Melissa Osborne.
It stars Asha Banks, Matthew Broome, Eve Macklin, Ray
Fearon, Sam Buchanan, and Jason Flemyng.
It is a remake of the 2023 Spanish film, My Fault, which is
based on the novel Culpa mía by Mercedes Ron.
It was released on Amazon Prime Video on 13 February 2025.
The film explores themes of based on novel or book,
release from prison, estranged father.
The tone is emotional.